FRIENDS, FAMILY, WE'RE GATHERED
TO CELEBRATE HERE TODAY
THE JOYOUS UNION
OF ROSS AND EMILY.
NOW, ROSS
REPEAT AFTER ME.
I, ROSS...
...TAKE THEE, EMILY...
...TAKE THEE, RACHEL...
( screaming )
EMILY.
( nervous chuckle ):
UH, SHALL I GO ON?
H-HE SAID RACHEL, RIGHT?
DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD GO UP THERE?
YES, YES, DO GO ON.
I THINK
WE'D BETTER START AGAIN.
ROSS, REPEAT AFTER ME.
I, ROSS...
...TAKE THEE, EMILY...
IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'D
BE ANYBODY ELSE.
...AS MY LAWFULLY WEDDED WIFE,
IN SICKNESS AND IN HEALTH
TILL DEATH PARTS US.
...AS MY LAWFULLY
WEDDED WIFE
IN SICKNESS
AND IN HEALTH
UNTIL DEATH PARTS US.
REALLY, I DO...
( giggle )
...EMILY.
DO WE HAVE
THE RINGS?
EMILY, PLACE THIS
RING ON ROSS' FINGER
AS A SYMBOL OF YOUR
BOND EVERLASTING.
AH!
ROSS,
PLACE THIS RING
ON EMILY'S HAND
AS A SYMBOL
OF THE LOVE
THAT ENCIRCLES YOU FOREVER.
HAPPY TO.
ROSS AND EMILY
HAVE MADE THEIR DECLARATION
AND IT GIVES ME GREAT PLEASURE
TO DECLARE THEM
HUSBAND AND WIFE.
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
THIS IS WORSE THAN WHEN
HE MARRIED THE LESBIAN.
JUST KEEP SMILING.
OKAY.
WELL, THAT WENT
WELL. YEAH.
COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE.
HE COULD HAVE SHOT HER.
( chuckling nervously )
THAT, UH, THAT WAS
PRETTY FUNNY, WASN'T IT?
( grunting )
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
Emily:
YOU SPOILED EVERYTHING!
IT'S LIKE A NIGHTMARE!
MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY
ARE OUT THERE!
HOW CAN I FACE THEM?
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME?!
HEY, NO MATTER
WHAT HAPPENS WITH
ROSS AND EMILY
WE STILL GET
CAKE, RIGHT?
T-THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU, NO, NO,
YOU TAKE YOUR TIME, SWEETIE.
I'LL BE RIGHT OUT HERE.
( nervous laugh )
SHE'S JUST FIXING HER MAKEUP.
Emily:
I HATE YOU!
AND I LOVE YOU!
BOY, BAD TIME TO SAY
THE WRONG NAME, HUH, ROSS?
THAT'S TRUE.
THANKS, DAD.
HEY, PEOPLE
SHOULD BE DANCING, HUH?
THIS IS A PARTY!
COME ON!
JOEY, DANCE!
( phone ringing )
YES, WALTHAM INTERIORS.
OH, HELLO, THIS
IS ROSS GELLER'S
PERSONAL PHYSICIAN,
DR. FILANGIE.
WHO?
YEAH. I'VE DISCOVERED
THAT ROSS FORGOT
TO TAKE HIS BRAIN MEDICINE.
UM, NOW, WITHOUT IT,
UH, IN THE BRAIN OF ROSS,
UH, WOMEN'S NAMES
ARE INTERCHANGEABLE...
THROUGH NO FAULT OF HIS OWN.
OH, MY GOD. PHOEBE.
NO, NOT PHOEBE.
DR. FILANGIE.
OH, NO, YOU HAVE IT, TOO!
HELLO?
( dial tone )
HEY.
OH, WOW, I HOPE YOU DON'T
TAKE THIS THE WRONG WAY, BUT
I KNOW WE HAD PLANS
TO MEET UP TONIGHT, AND...
AH, I'M JUST,
I'M KIND OF WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT IT MIGHT DO
TO OUR FRIENDSHIP.
I KNOW.
OH, HOW COULD WE
HAVE LET THIS HAPPEN?
SEVEN TIMES!
WELL, YOU KNOW,
LOOK, WE WERE AWAY.
IN A FOREIGN,
ROMANTIC COUNTRY.
I BLAME LONDON.
BAD LONDON!
SO, LOOK, UM WHILE
WE'RE STILL IN LONDON,
I MEAN, WE CAN KEEP
DOING IT, RIGHT?
WELL, I DON'T SEE
THAT WE HAVE A CHOICE.
NO.
BUT WHEN WE'RE BACK
HOME, WE DON'T DO IT.
ONLY HERE.
YOU KNOW, I SAW A
WINE CELLAR DOWNSTAIRS.
MEET YOU THERE
IN TWO MINUTES.
'KAY.
MON, HONEY,
I GOT TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
NOW?
ROSS SAID MY NAME UP THERE.
I MEAN, COME ON,
I CAN'T JUST PRETEND
THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN, CAN I?
OH, I-I DON'T KNOW.
MONICA, WHAT SHOULD I DO?
JUST, UH...
DO THE RIGHT THING.
WHAT?
TOE THE LINE.
THREAD THE NEEDLE.
THINK OUTSIDE THE BOX.
MONICA, WAIT.
I THINK I'M JUST GONNA
TALK TO ROSS ABOUT
WHAT HE THINKS IT MEANT.
WAIT. RACHEL, NO.
HE'S MARRIED.
MARRIED.
IF YOU DON'T REALIZE THAT,
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
OKAY. YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T HELP ME.
JACK, IS IT ALL OUR FAULT?
WERE WE BAD PARENTS?
YES.
OH, YEAH? WELL,
WHO SERVES STEAK
WHEN THERE'S NO
PLACE TO SIT?
I MEAN, HOW ARE
YOU SUPPOSED
TO EAT THIS?
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
WHERE WERE YOU?
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO MEET
IN THE WINE CELLAR.
FORGET IT.
THAT'S OFF.
WHY?
( drunkenly ):
THE NEXT TOUR OF
THE WINE CELLAR
WILL COMMENCE
IN TWO MI-I-INUTES.
JOEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU PROMISED PHOEBE
YOU WOULDN'T EAT MEAT
UNTIL SHE HAS THE BABIES.
OH, I FIGURED
WE'RE IN ANOTHER COUNTRY
SO IT DOESN'T COUNT.
WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
THE MAN'S GOT A POINT.
OH, HI.
HI.
I'M SORRY THINGS
AREN'T WORKING OUT SO WELL.
OH, NO!
( nervous chuckle )
COULD BE BETTER.
IT'S GONNA
BE OKAY, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH, OF COURSE.
I MEAN, SHE'S GONNA
GET OVER THIS, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN,
SO YOU SAID MY NAME.
YOU KNOW, YOU JUST SAID IT
'CAUSE YOU SAW ME THERE.
IF YOU'D SEEN
A CIRCUS FREAK
YOU WOULD'VE SAID,
"I TAKE THEE, CIRCUS FREAK."
YOU KNOW,
IT DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST A MISTAKE.
DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
RIGHT?
OH, NO, OF COURSE
IT DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
I MEAN, WHA... I CAN
UNDERSTAND WHY EMILY
WOULD THINK IT
MEANT SOMETHING
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE IT WAS YOU,
BUT IT ABSOLUTELY DIDN'T.
IT DIDN'T! IT DIDN'T!
ROSS! HEY,
THE BAND'S READY OUTSIDE
FOR YOUR FIRST DANCE
WITH EMILY, SO...
OH! OH!
THE BAND'S READY!
WELL, WE'VE GOT TO DO
WHAT THE BAND SAYS, RIGHT?
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE STUPID BAND!
YOU SPIT ON ME, MAN.
I-I'M SORRY.
EMILY IS TAKING
KIND OF A LONG TIME, HUH?
YOU KNOW, WHEN I LOCKED MYSELF
IN THE BATHROOM AT MY WEDDING
IT WAS BECAUSE
I WAS TRYING
TO POP THE WINDOW
OUT OF THE FRAME,
OH, RIGHT.
AND GET THE HELL
OUT OF THERE, YOU KNOW?
( chuckling nervously )
EMILY?
EMILY?!
I'M COMING IN!
WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
SAME THING.
LISTEN, IN THE MIDDLE
OF EVERYTHING
IF I SCREAM THE WORD "YIPPEE,"
JUST IGNORE ME.
( gasping )
OH, MY GOD, RACHEL! HI.
OH, HELLO, RACHEL.
ROSS SAID MY NAME.
OKAY? MY NAME.
ROSS SAID MY
NAME UP THERE.
THAT OBVIOUSLY MEANS
THAT HE STILL LOVES ME.
OKAY, DON'T BELIEVE ME.
I KNOW I'M RIGHT.
DO YOU GUYS WANT TO GO
DOWNSTAIRS AND GET A DRINK?
YES, WE DO.
BUT WE HAVE
TO CHANGE FIRST.
YES, I WANT TO CHANGE.
W-WHY DON'T YOU GO DOWN
AND GET US A TABLE?
YEAH, WE'LL BE DOWN
IN, LIKE, FIVE MINUTES.
15 MINUTES.
OKAY.
( phone ringing )
HELLO. OH, PHEEBS!
IT'S PHOEBE.
( mumbling politely )
HI!
SO, WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, ROSS SAID MY NAME.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT I DON'T THINK
THAT MEANS ANYTHING.
OKAY, PHEEBS, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S LOOK AT THIS OBJECTIVELY.
ALL RIGHT, NINTH GRADE, RIGHT?
THE OBSESSION STARTS.
ALL RIGHT? SUMMER
AFTER NINTH GRADE
HE SEES ME IN A TWO-PIECE
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
HIS OBSESSION BEGINS TO GROW,
RIGHT? SO, THEN...
HEY, LISTEN, WHY DON'T
WE GO CHANGE IN MY ROOM?
MY CLOTHES ARE... OH!
( chuckling )
WOW, YOU LOOK...
NO TIME FOR THAT.
OKAY.
HEY, DUDE, LET ME IN.
I GOT A GIRL OUT HERE.
WELL, I'VE GOT
A GIRL IN HERE.
NO, YOU DON'T.
I JUST SAW YOU GO
IN THERE WITH MONICA.
WELL, WE'RE
HANGING OUT IN HERE.
WHICH ONE OF US IS GOING TO BE
HAVING SEX IN THERE, ME OR YOU?
WELL, I SUPPOSE
I WOULD HAVE TO SAY YOU.
LOOK, WHAT IF WE'RE WATCHING
A MOVIE IN HERE?
W-WHICH WE ARE.
A-AND WE ALREADY PAID FOR IT.
IT'S MY GIANT.
MY GIANT?
I LOVE THAT MOVIE!
YOU REALLY THINK
THIS IS OKAY?
WELL, ROSS AND EMILY
AREN'T GOING TO USE IT.
OH, IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL!
OH!
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
IF I FEEL RIGHT ABOUT THIS.
OH, M-MON, MON, M-M-MONICA...
THIS IS THE HONEYMOON SUITE.
THE ROOM EXPECTS SEX.
THE ROOM WOULD BE DISAPPOINTED
IF IT DIDN'T GET SEX.
ALL OF THE OTHER
HONEYMOON SUITES WOULD
THINK IT WAS A LOSER.
OKAY.
EMILY?
NOPE, NOT UNDER HERE.
YOU DIDN'T FIND HER?
NO. I'VE LOOKED EVERYWHERE.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE LOOKED
EVERYWHERE
OR ELSE
YOU WOULD'VE FOUND HER.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
KEEP LOOKING.
YEAH, FOR ABOUT, UH, 30 MINUTES.
OR 45?
WOW, IN 45 MINUTES,
YOU COULD FIND HER TWICE.
NO. FOR ALL I KNOW,
SHE'S TRYING TO FIND ME,
BUT COULDN'T
BECAUSE I KEPT
MOVING AROUND.
NO, FROM NOW ON,
I'M STAYING IN ONE PLACE.
RIGHT HERE.
WELL, IT'S GETTING LATE.
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO G--
YOU GUYS MIND
STAYING HERE FOR A WHILE?
YOU KNOW, UM,
WE GOT TO GET UP EARLY
AND CATCH THAT PLANE
TO NEW YORK.
YEAH, IT'S A
VERY LARGE PLANE.
THAT'S COOL.
BUT WE'LL STAY HERE
WITH YOU.
THANKS, GUYS!
I REALLY APPRECIATE THIS,
YOU KNOW?
BUT YOU DON'T NEED
TO RUB MY BUTT.
WE HAVE TO LEAVE
FOR NEW YORK IN AN HOUR.
I KNOW. I'VE BEEN
LOOKING AT THOSE DOORS.
THEY LOOK SOUNDPROOF,
DON'T YOU THINK?
WE CAN'T DO THAT.
THAT'S INSANE.
I MEAN, A: HE COULD WAKE UP.
AND B: YOU KNOW...
LET'S GO FOR IT.
( knocking on door )
EMIL... EMILY?
EM... EMILY!
EMILY!
NO.
YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT EMILY,
SHE'S NOT WITH US.
WE'VE COME FOR
HER THINGS.
W-WHERE IS SHE?
SHE'S IN HIDING.
SHE'S UTTERLY HUMILIATED.
SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO SEE YOU EVER AGAIN.
WE'RE VERY SAD THAT
IT DIDN'T WORK OUT
BETWEEN YOU AND EMILY...
MONKEY.
BUT I THINK YOU'RE
ABSOLUTELY DELICIOUS.
EXCUSE ME. I'M
STANDING RIGHT HERE.
OH, YES.
THERE YOU ARE.
HEY! HEY, YOU GUYS!
GO HURRY UP, GET SOME.
THERE'S A WHOLE CART OUTSIDE.
BYE, GELLER.
WAIT, HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
LOOK, LOOK...
YOUR DAUGHTER AND I
ARE SUPPOSED TO LEAVE
TONIGHT FOR OUR HONEYMOON.
NOW... NOW YOU TELL HER
THAT I'M GOING TO BE
AT THAT AIRPORT
AND I HOPE THAT
SHE'LL BE THERE, TOO.
OH, YEAH, I SAID
RACHEL'S NAME
BUT IT DIDN'T MEAN
ANYTHING, OKAY?
SHE'S JUST A FRIEND.
THAT'S ALL.
NOW, LOOK, JUST TELL
EMILY THAT I LOVE HER
AND THAT I CAN'T IMAGINE
SPENDING MY LIFE
WITH ANYONE ELSE.
PLEASE, PROMISE ME THAT
YOU'LL TELL HER THAT.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL TELL HER.
COME ON, BUGGERFACE.
CALL ME.
( gasps )
YOU SPEND HALF YOUR
LIFE IN THE BATHROOM.
WHY DO YOU NEVER GO
OUT THE BLOODY WINDOW?
YOU KNOW, MAYBE IT'S BEST
WE NEVER GOT TO DO IT AGAIN.
YEAH, IT KIND OF MAKES
THAT ONE NIGHT SPECIAL.
YOU KNOW, TECHNICALLY
WE STILL ARE OVER
INTERNATIONAL WATERS.
I'M GOING TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
MAYBE I'LL SEE YOU
THERE IN A BIT?
OKAY.
HEY, CAN I ASK
YOU SOMETHING?
UH... NO.
FELICITY AND I, WE'RE
WATCHING MY GIANT, RIGHT?
AND I WAS THINKING,
I'M NEVER GOING TO BE
AS GOOD AN ACTOR
AS THAT GIANT.
DO YOU THINK I'M
JUST WASTING MY LIFE
WITH THIS ACTING THING?
NO.
THE GIANT'S, LIKE,
FIVE YEARS YOUNGER
THAN ME, YOU KNOW?
YOU THINK I'LL
EVER GET THERE?
YES.
THANKS, MAN.
OKAY, MAN.
BUT WHAT ABOUT HOW MUCH
TALLER HE IS THAN ME?
I MEAN, THERE'S
NO WAY I CAN MAKE
MYSELF TALLER NOW.
YOU KNOW? AND WHO KNOWS
WHAT SCIENCE WILL COME UP
WITH IN THE FUTURE?
BUT, CHANDLER,
WHAT IF I DIE
AN UNSUCCESSFUL,
REGULAR-SIZE MAN?
HEY, MONICA. YOU BEEN
IN THE BATHROOM FOR,
LIKE, A HALF HOUR.
I KNOW.
HAD THE BEEF TIPS, HUH?
( giggles )
HEY!
HI!
( laughing )
YOU ATE MEAT.
YOU HAD SEX!
NO, WE DIDN'T.
I KNOW YOU DIDN'T.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT MONICA.
PHOEBE, I DID
NOT HAVE SEX.
OH, THIS PREGNANCY IS
THROWING ME ALL OFF.
I'M GONNA GO SAY HI
TO THE CHICK AND THE DUCK.
OH, ME, TOO.
WHY WOULD YOU NEED
TO SAY HI TO THEM?
YOU'VE BEEN FEEDING THEM
FOR FOUR DAYS.
OH, RIGHT. MAYBE
I'LL JUST GO HOME.
WELL, WE CERTAINLY
ARE ALONE.
YES, GOOD THING WE HAD
THAT "NOT IN NEW YORK" RULE.
RIGHT.
UM, LISTEN, SINCE
WE'RE ON THAT SUBJECT...
I JUST WANTED
TO TELL YOU THAT, UM,
WELL... I WAS GOING THROUGH
A REALLY HARD TIME IN LONDON
WHAT WITH MY BROTHER
GETTING MARRIED
AND THAT GUY THINKING
I WAS ROSS'S MOTHER.
RIGHT.
WELL, ANYWAY, I JUST...
THAT NIGHT MEANT
A LOT TO ME
AND I GUESS I'M TRYING
TO SAY THANKS.
OH.
YOU KNOW, THAT NIGHT MEANT
A LOT TO ME, TOO.
AND IT WASN'T 'CAUSE I WAS
IN A BAD PLACE OR ANYTHING.
IT JUST MEANT A LOT TO ME
'CAUSE... YOU'RE REALLY HOT.
IS THAT OKAY?
THAT'S OKAY.
AND I'M CUTE, TOO.
AND YOU'RE CUTE, TOO.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE GOT TO GO UNPACK.
OKAY.
BYE.
I'M STILL ON LONDON TIME.
DOES THAT COUNT?
OH, THAT COUNTS.
OH, GOOD.
RACH!
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL, I'VE BEEN ON STANDBY
FOR A FLIGHT HOME FOR HOURS.
OH.
OH... SO NO SIGN
OF EMILY, HUH?
NOT YET.
SO, UM, WHAT TIME ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO LEAVE?
P.A.:
This is the last call
for flight 1066 to Athens.
The last call.
PRETTY SOON, I GUESS.
YEAH.
I'M SORRY.
I JUST... I DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, HOW COULD SHE DO THIS?
AM I, LIKE, A COMPLETE IDIOT
FOR THINKING SHE'D
ACTUALLY SHOW UP?
NO, YOU'RE NOT AN IDIOT, ROSS.
YOU'RE A GUY VERY MUCH IN LOVE.
SAME DIFFERENCE.
All ticketed passengers
for flight 1066 to Athens
should now be on board.
I GET IT!
WELL, THAT'S THAT.
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO.
WHAT?
YEAH, I DO.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO
BY YOURSELF.
GET SOME DISTANCE.
CLEAR YOUR HEAD.
I THINK IT WOULD BE
REALLY GOOD.
OH, I DON'T, I DON'T KNOW.
OH, COME ON, ROSS.
I THINK IT WOULD BE
REALLY GOOD FOR YOU.
I... I... I COULD.
I-I COULD DO THAT.
YEAH.
I CAN'T EVEN BELIEVE HER.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM GOING TO GO.
GOOD.
WHY NOT?
RIGHT!
RIGHT?
THANKS.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU
BACK AT HOME...
IF I EVER GET A FLIGHT.
HEY, WH... NAH.
WHAT? WAIT. WHAT?
WHY DON'T YOU COME?
I MEAN, I HAVE TWO TICKETS.
WHY NOT?
( mumbling ):
WELL, ROSS, I...
REALLY?
YEAH, YEAH, IT'D BE GREAT.
I MEAN, YOU CAN
LAY ON THE BEACH
AND I CAN CRY OVER
MY FAILED MARRIAGE.
SEE HOW I MAKE JOKES?
UH-HUH.
NO, REALLY, I MEAN...
GOD, I COULD USE A FRIEND.
OH, WOW, OKAY... UH, MAYBE.
UM...
YES, I CAN DO THAT.
OKAY, COOL.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, COOL.
OKAY, WE'RE GOING
TO GREECE.
AH! I FORGOT MY JACKET.
TELL THEM TO WAIT.
Rachel:
WAIT! WAIT!
EMILY.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO...
NO! NO!
EMILY!
UH, YES, I WILL HAVE
A GLASS OF THE MERLOT,
AND HE WILL HAVE A
WHITE WINE SPRITZER.
WHOO.
( chuckling )
HEY, LOOK AT THAT,
THE AIRPORT'S MOVING.
HEY, ARE WE MOVING?
ARE WE MOVING?
WHY ARE WE MOVING?
THAT DOESN'T...
UM, YEAH, DOES THE CAPTAIN KNOW
THAT WE'RE MOVING?
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOSH.